<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Upadesh Shrestha</title>
    <link href="https://upadesh.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://upadesh.github.io" />
    <updated>2020-05-10T19:21:11+05:45</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Upadesh Shrestha</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://upadesh.github.io</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Lenovo K4 Note</title>
        <author>
            <name>Upadesh Shrestha</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://upadesh.github.io/lenovo-k4-note.html"/>
        <id>https://upadesh.github.io/lenovo-k4-note.html</id>
            <category term="Lenevo"/>
            <category term="Android Phone"/>

        <updated>2020-04-20T10:02:52+05:45</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/64/lenevo-k4-note.jpg" alt="" />
                    Lenovo K4 Note is Android v5.1 (Lollipop) based phone with Vibe UI in the top at रु. 24000. It is Dual SIM, GSM+GSM 4G, 3G, 2G enabled device with 3300 mAh battery of Li-Polymer capacity. Lenovo K4 Note has 5.5 inches screen size touch screen&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/64/lenevo-k4-note.jpg" alt="" />
                <p style="text-align: justify;">Lenovo K4 Note is Android v5.1 (Lollipop) based phone with Vibe UI in the top at रु. 24000. It is Dual SIM, GSM+GSM 4G, 3G, 2G enabled device with 3300 mAh battery of Li-Polymer capacity. Lenovo K4 Note has 5.5 inches screen size touch screen and has the resolution of Full HD (1080 x 1920 pixels) with pixel density of 401 ppi. Phone comes with IPS LCD Capacitive Touchscreen, Multi-touch with Corning Gorilla Glass v3 as screen protection.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Lenovo K4 Note is powered by Octa core, 1.3 GHz, Cortex A53 MediaTek MT6753 64 bit processor with 3 GB of RAM. The phone packs 16 GB of internal storage that can be expanded up to 128 GB via a microSD card.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Lenovo K4 Note has 13 MP main camera with features like Exposure compensation, ISO control, Continuos Shooting, High Dynamic Range mode (HDR) and 5 MP front camera with Fixed Focus.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Lenovo K4 Note measures 153.6 (H) x 76.5 (W) x 9.15 (T) mm and weighs 160 grams. It has connectivity options of Wi-Fi 802.11, a/ac/b/g/n, Bluetooth v4.0 and microUSB 2.0. It has multimedia features of Audio Jack 3.5 mm, Dolby Atmos and sensors in the phone include Fingerprint Sensor, Light sensor, Proximity sensor, Accelerometer, Compass, Gyroscope.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Top List of PHP Blogs</title>
        <author>
            <name>Upadesh Shrestha</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://upadesh.github.io/top-list-of-php-blogs.html"/>
        <id>https://upadesh.github.io/top-list-of-php-blogs.html</id>
            <category term="Webscripts"/>
            <category term="PHP Scripts"/>
            <category term="Blogs"/>

        <updated>2020-04-20T11:01:02+05:45</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    A blog (or weblog) is an online personal journal that is frequently updated and used for the general public. The blog is determined by their format: a wide range of items are taken on a single page in order. Blogs back in time often represent&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>A blog (or weblog) is an online personal journal that is frequently updated and used for the general public. The blog is determined by their format: a wide range of items are taken on a single page in order. Blogs back in time often represent the personality of the author or reflect the purpose of the web site that hosts the blog. Topics sometimes include brief philosophical musings, commentary on the Internet and other social issues, and links to other sites the author favors, especially those who support a point being made on a post.</p>
<p>Below are the list of blogs written in PHP which can be used with any kind of paid or free web hosts.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Video Template for Blogger</title>
        <author>
            <name>Upadesh Shrestha</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://upadesh.github.io/video-template-for-blogger.html"/>
        <id>https://upadesh.github.io/video-template-for-blogger.html</id>
            <category term="Web Scripts"/>
            <category term="Themes"/>
            <category term="Customization"/>
            <category term="Blogger Templates"/>

        <updated>2020-04-20T10:02:50+05:45</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/63/videoservices_600x300.png" alt="" />
                    You can make your own video site like YouTube or Vimeo in blogger with the list of blogger template listed below. You can customize these template to make the collection of videos, movies or anything you want to.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/63/videoservices_600x300.png" alt="" />
                <p>You can make your own video site like YouTube or Vimeo in blogger with the list of blogger template listed below. You can customize these template to make the collection of videos, movies or anything you want to.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Mero Love Story</title>
        <author>
            <name>Upadesh Shrestha</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://upadesh.github.io/mero-love-story.html"/>
        <id>https://upadesh.github.io/mero-love-story.html</id>
            <category term="Nepali Movies"/>
            <category term="Nepali Media"/>
            <category term="Entertainment"/>

        <updated>2020-04-20T10:02:49+05:45</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/62/mero-love-story-nepali-movie-poster.jpg" alt="" />
                    [jwplayer agw6WFxx-pxatGdXV]
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/62/mero-love-story-nepali-movie-poster.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>[jwplayer agw6WFxx-pxatGdXV]</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Chha Ekan Chha</title>
        <author>
            <name>Upadesh Shrestha</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://upadesh.github.io/chha-ekan-chha.html"/>
        <id>https://upadesh.github.io/chha-ekan-chha.html</id>
            <category term="Nepali Movies"/>
            <category term="Nepali Media"/>
            <category term="Entertainment"/>

        <updated>2020-04-20T10:02:48+05:45</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/61/chha-ekan-chha-nepali-movie-poster.jpg" alt="" />
                    [jwplayer dhCZak1p-4kjKOgCH]
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/61/chha-ekan-chha-nepali-movie-poster.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>[jwplayer dhCZak1p-4kjKOgCH]</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>5 Highest Selling Brands of 2015 in Nepal</title>
        <author>
            <name>Upadesh Shrestha</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://upadesh.github.io/5-highest-selling-brands-of-2015-in-nepal.html"/>
        <id>https://upadesh.github.io/5-highest-selling-brands-of-2015-in-nepal.html</id>

        <updated>2020-04-20T10:02:47+05:45</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/60/header.jpg" alt="" />
                    Nepal is one of the newly emerging and growing economies of the world. The country has seen a rise in many different aspects all around such as the infrastructure, technology, communications and many more. Due to these changes, many major brands have a great standing&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/60/header.jpg" alt="" />
                <p style="text-align: justify">Nepal is one of the newly emerging and growing economies of the world. The country has seen a rise in many different aspects all around such as the infrastructure, technology, communications and many more. Due to these changes, many major brands have a great standing in the Nepali market. More and more people demand the latest products by these brands to have in their possession and value the money they spend on them. Many stores now keep some of the highest selling brand’s products with them and a number of online marketplaces such as <a href="http://www.kaymu.com.np/">Kaymu</a> and <a href="http://hamrobazaar.com/">Hamro Bazaar</a> stock up on the latest items needed by the people of Nepal, for their easy accessibility.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">There are many brands that were dominating the market but the leading ones left the rest far back. Here are some of the names that you can immediately recognize:</p>
<ol style="text-align: justify">
<li><strong>Apple:</strong></li>
</ol>
<p style="text-align: justify">Everyone knows what <a href="http://www.forbes.com/companies/apple/">Apple</a> is. This company is known to design, manufacture and market mobile communication and media devices, computers, digital music players, software, networking solutions and many more. The major products include the iPhone, iPad, iPod, Mac and Apple TV.</p>
<p><img class=" wp-image-944 aligncenter" src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/60/apple-300x169.jpg" alt="apple" width="362" height="204" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">When it comes to the highest selling products, you can see the iPhone. With its launch a few years back, it took the world with a storm. Now every year, the company launches a newer version with higher levels of features for everyone to enjoy. They run on the iOS operating system and have facilities such as Apple Music, iCloud and much more.</p>
<ol style="text-align: justify" start="2">
<li><strong>Samsung:</strong></li>
</ol>
<p style="text-align: justify"><a href="http://www.samsung.com/">Samsung</a> is popularly known as one of the largest multinational electronics giants out there. With its basis in Seoul, South Korea, it has a huge presence in more than a hundred countries worldwide. It is famous all over the world due to its large product portfolio that has products that suit each and every lifestyle. All the items in their range ensure superior quality and high durability.</p>
<p><img class=" wp-image-945 aligncenter" src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/60/samsung-300x169.jpg" alt="samsung" width="392" height="221" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">The Samsung Mobile is considered to be one of a kind as there is a huge demand for it. They offer the latest looks along with the features to match. Every year the brand is in competition with other famous ones to launch best device. Their phones start from the basics and go up to high quality smartphones with the latest Android operating systems. With high stability, good designs and an amazing overall experience, these are the best for anyone.</p>
<ol style="text-align: justify" start="3">
<li><strong>Casio:</strong></li>
</ol>
<p style="text-align: justify"><a href="http://www.casio-intl.com/np/en/">Casio</a> is one of the most famous brands all around the world and Nepal is no exception to this. It is a multinational electronics manufacturing company located in Japan and it offers many products for everyday and special uses. The products include calculators, mobile phones, musical instruments and watches.</p>
<p><img class=" wp-image-946 aligncenter" src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/60/casio-300x194.jpg" alt="casio" width="414" height="268" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">When it comes to the highest selling items, the brand offers watches that can be used for active, luxurious or comfortable lifestyles. Originally, they started off with base line models with the simple minimum sum of features and over the years they have added many new additional ones which set them apart from other brands. The Casio Digital and Analogue watches are the two types they sell with the most popular one being the G Shock which is much loved by all men.</p>
<ol style="text-align: justify" start="4">
<li><strong>Beats Headphones: </strong></li>
</ol>
<p style="text-align: justify"><a href="http://www.beatsbydre.com/">Beats</a> headphones and headsets have taken the world by storm. With ultimate superior sound quality and gorgeous colors, they are a most loved item by many people out there. Developed by the rapper and artist, Dr. Dre, they are a hit among the youth especially.</p>
<p><img class=" wp-image-947 aligncenter" src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/60/beats-300x163.jpg" alt="beats" width="530" height="288" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">There are different types of headphones available of the brand and each is suited to the varied requirements of people. The Beats by Dr Dre Studio headphones are the most popular ones out there. The highly attractive feature present in them is the noise cancellation element. All these models require high functioning batteries in order to operate. The Beats by Dr Dre Pro are the best option when it comes to in studio usage. These ones come in stainless steel aluminum coverage, giving them an ultimate look</p>
<ol style="text-align: justify" start="5">
<li><strong>Hewlett Packard:</strong></li>
</ol>
<p style="text-align: justify"><a href="http://www.hp.com/">Hewlett Packard</a> started its business in California and over the period of many years, has established itself in more than 150 countries worldwide. It has a wide range of devices in its portfolio that provide everyday solutions to its users such as a HP printer or notebook.</p>
<p><img class=" wp-image-948 aligncenter" src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/60/hp-300x168.jpg" alt="hp" width="462" height="259" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">When it comes to their most selling item, the HP Laptop dominates over anything else. These products are high functioning with the looks to match. Each of their features are made in a way that they can last for a really long time with the proper functioning elements.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Online Shopping Sites in Nepal</title>
        <author>
            <name>Upadesh Shrestha</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://upadesh.github.io/online-shopping-sites-in-nepal.html"/>
        <id>https://upadesh.github.io/online-shopping-sites-in-nepal.html</id>
            <category term="Online Shopping"/>
            <category term="Nepal"/>

        <updated>2020-04-20T10:02:46+05:45</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/59/online-shopping.jpg" alt="" />
                    With the increase in craze for online shopping and wider accessibility to internet, lots of online store has been started in Nepal with motive to provide home shopping with just few clicks. There are still lots of advantages and disadvantages of online shopping but with the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/59/online-shopping.jpg" alt="" />
                <p style="text-align: justify;">With the increase in craze for online shopping and wider accessibility to internet, lots of online store has been started in Nepal with motive to provide home shopping with just few clicks. There are still lots of advantages and disadvantages of online shopping but with the establishment of big stores and its demand for shopping has made these site more user-friendly and trusted. To point out its advantages, one can buy it just staying in home and comparing the huge variety of items with price, which make the buyer more easier and confident. But some of the disadvantages are that the product might not be what that appears on their screen, shipping limited to few of the places, online payment instead of cash on delivery and hectic replacement procedure. In this post, I am going to list out the online shopping sites that are working actively in Nepali market. If you like this post please share and comment.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Disclaimer: I am not responsible for any inconvenience caused by any sites listed below and it is solely dependent on your choice of site selections.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Giant Anthem Advanced 27.5 1</title>
        <author>
            <name>Upadesh Shrestha</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://upadesh.github.io/giant-anthem-advanced-275-1.html"/>
        <id>https://upadesh.github.io/giant-anthem-advanced-275-1.html</id>
            <category term="Mountain Bikes"/>
            <category term="Giant Anthem"/>
            <category term="Cycles"/>

        <updated>2020-04-20T10:02:45+05:45</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/58/Giant-Anthem-Advanced-27.5-1.jpg" alt="" />
                    Giant Anthem Advanced 27.5 1 is Mountain Dual Suspension type bike with top speed of 30 gears which might cost approxmately रु. 5,02,000 in Nepal. The weight of bicycle is 12 kg and available in size of S, M, L, XL with the color varient&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/58/Giant-Anthem-Advanced-27.5-1.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>Giant Anthem Advanced 27.5 1 is Mountain Dual Suspension type bike with top speed of 30 gears which might cost approxmately रु. 5,02,000 in Nepal. The weight of bicycle is 12 kg and available in size of S, M, L, XL with the color varient of Silver/Blue.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Giant XTC Advanced 29er 1</title>
        <author>
            <name>Upadesh Shrestha</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://upadesh.github.io/giant-xtc-advanced-29er-1.html"/>
        <id>https://upadesh.github.io/giant-xtc-advanced-29er-1.html</id>
            <category term="Mountain Bikes"/>
            <category term="Cycles"/>

        <updated>2020-04-20T10:02:44+05:45</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/57/giant-xtc-advanced-29er11.jpg" alt="" />
                    Giant XTC Advanced 29er 1 is Mountain Hardtail type bike with top speed of 30 gears which might cost approxmately रु. 2,80,000 in Nepal. The weight of bicycle is 5 kg and available in size of S, M, L, XL with the color varient of&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/57/giant-xtc-advanced-29er11.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>Giant XTC Advanced 29er 1 is Mountain Hardtail type bike with top speed of 30 gears which might cost approxmately रु. 2,80,000 in Nepal. The weight of bicycle is 5 kg and available in size of S, M, L, XL with the color varient of Metallic Blue/Blue.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Himshikhar Television</title>
        <author>
            <name>Upadesh Shrestha</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://upadesh.github.io/himshikhar-television.html"/>
        <id>https://upadesh.github.io/himshikhar-television.html</id>
            <category term="Online TV"/>
            <category term="Nepali Television"/>
            <category term="Nepali Media"/>

        <updated>2020-04-20T10:02:42+05:45</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/56/himshikar-logo.png" alt="" />
                    [jwplayer mediaid="490"]Himshikhar Television is a 24hrs Nepali TV Channel with Instant news, information and entertainment stuffs. Himshikhar Television started broadcasting from the month of Kartik 2067, as private channel by Himshikhar Media Group of Eastern Nepal with a slogan ‘Education,Information and Entertainment’.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://upadesh.github.io/media/posts/56/himshikar-logo.png" alt="" />
                <p>[jwplayer mediaid="490"]Himshikhar Television is a 24hrs Nepali TV Channel with Instant news, information and entertainment stuffs. Himshikhar Television started broadcasting from the month of Kartik 2067, as private channel by Himshikhar Media Group of Eastern Nepal with a slogan ‘Education,Information and Entertainment’.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
